funkykit.com 2019-07-14

# Privacy - FunkyKit

Funky Kit recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of our readers. Funky Kit does not collect personal information about our readers except for information that may be voluntarily provided. We do set cookies occasionally in order to better understand our readers’ Funky Kit experiences. No personal information is gathered via these cookies.

Personally information is treated confidentially should you volunteer it via email or via a survey. We consider the following to be personal information: your name, address, phone number, date of birth, job, personal interests, credit card information, your e-mail address and data about the pages you visited at Funky Kit.

**About our Adverts**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**Legal Disclaimer**

All the information and contents posted on this Web Site are the property of Funky Kit and are protected by U.S., U.K. and foreign copyright and trademark laws. By accessing this Web Site, you agree to the following terms and conditions. If you do not agree, you have no right to use this Web Site.

  * This Web Site and its contents may not be copied or distributed in any manner without the prior written consent of Funky Kit. With the following exception:  
You may copy up to 2 paragraphs per article provided that you attribute the material to [www.FunkyKit.com](http://www.funkykit.com/)

  * Funky Kit MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES WITH RESPECT TO THIS WEB SITE, ITS CONTENTS OR THE MANUSCRIPT, WHICH ARE PROVIDED FOR USE “AS IS” AND IS WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND.

  * Portions of this Web Site may publish readers’ comments and opinion. Funky Kit does not assume or have any responsibility or any liability for the readers’ comments or opinions.

If you have questions about our privacy or legal policies, contact us by e-mail at [webmaster@funkykit.com](mailto:webmaster@funkykit.com)

## Update: GDPR – What personal data we collect and why we collect it

By default we does not collect any personal data about visitors, and only collects the data shown on the User Profile screen from registered users. However some of the 3rd party plugins we use may collect personal data. You may want to contact us before accessing the content of our website.

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website. All uploaded files are usually publicly accessible.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### **Analytics**

By default we does not collect any analytics data. However, many web hosting accounts collect some anonymous analytics data. We have installed a Google Analytics plugin that provides analytics services. 

### Who we share your data with

WE DO NOT share any personal data with anyone.

### How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

### What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

### Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

### Your contact information

In this section you should provide a contact method for privacy-specific concerns. If you are required to have a Data Protection Officer, list their name and full contact details here as well.

### How we protect your data

We use Amazon Web services. All data protected is handled by AWS.

### What data breach procedures we have in place

If there is a data breach we will announce it on our social media platforms and on our website.
